我将去往南方公园 度过一段时光
I'm going out to South Park gonna have myself a time
处处是无欲谦人 友善面庞
Friendly faces everywhere humble folks without temptation
我将去往南方公园 远离我的悲伤
I'm goin out to south park gonna leave my woes behind
日夜都有充足车位 邻居人人礼貌大方
Ample parking day or night people spouting howdy neighbor
我将去往南方公园 试着放松一场
I'm heading out to south park to see if i cant unwind
我爱女孩 大奶成双
I like girls with big fat titties really big fat titties
快来南方公园吧 与我的朋友会一场
So come on out to south park and meet some friends of mine
南方公园 第11季第2集 "Cartman吸了（双关语：Cartman锉了）"
Episode 11x02 "Cartman Sucks"
这张照片我把它叫做"皮埃尔"
This picture I like to call "The Pierre."
我邀请Butters来过夜
I invited Butters to stay the night.
他睡着的时候 我用猫屎在他脸上做了胡子
And while he was sleeping I made a mustache on his face with cat poo.
还有这次Butters过夜的时候 我把卫生棉棒塞到他嘴里
And this time, when Butters stayed the night, I put a tampon in his mouth.
我把这幅叫做"沉睡月经"
I call this picture "The Sleeping Menstrual."
这幅我叫做“星期一热软糖”
This one, I call "Hot Fudge Mondae."
我特别喜欢这幅的背景光
I really like how the light plays with the background on this one.
-你把我们喊过来就为看这个？ -哦 不 还有好多
Is this all you brought us here to see? - Oh no, there's much more.
我们看看 哦 对了 看看这幅 我称之为“新月升起”
Let's see. Oh yes, look at this one. I call it "New Moon Rising."
如何用屁股我可做了好多研究
I did a whole study using my ass.
这副用的是高对比度
Here it is using some high-contrast stuff.
试了不同的滤光器
Trying out some different light filters here.
不过都不比上今天我计划做的
But this is nothing compared to what I have planned.
因为今晚就是我的致命一击
Because tonight is going to be my coup de grace.
-Butters今晚过来过夜？ -是的
Butters is staying over tonight? - Yes.
今晚 当Butters睡着时 我将－
And tonight, while Butters is asleep, I am going to-
嗨 伙计们
Hey, fellas!
哦 嗨 Butters！我没想到你这么快
Oh, oh hey, Butters! I wasn't expecting you so soon.
对 我做完家务 所以就早点过来了
Yeah. I finished my chores so I came over a little early.
-嗨 你们都留下来过夜吗？ -不 不 这些家伙就走了
Hey! Are you guys all sleeping over too? - No, no, these guys were just leaving.
伙计们 对吧？
Weren't you guys?
快点 我们走吧
Come on, let's go.
等等 我不能让这个发生
Wait, wait, I can't let this happen.
-Butters -嗯 Kyle？
Butters. - Yeah, Kyle?
你不觉得Cartman老是请你过夜有点奇怪吗？
Don't you think it's a little strange that Cartman keeps asking you to stay over?
Kyle！
Kyle!
-你是什么意思？ -我的意思是 如果－
What do you mean? - I mean, that if-
他的意思就是 他嫉妒你取代他 成为我最好的朋友！
What he means is that he's jealous that you've taken his place as my new best friend!
但是 成熟点吧 Kyle！ 变化是生活的一部分
But grow up, Kyle! Change is a part of life.
对啊 成熟起来 Kyle
Yeah, grow up, Kyle.
Eric 你想先做什么？ 你想玩游戏还是聊会儿天？
So what do you wanna do first, Eric? You wanna play a game or just chitchat for a while?
嗯 其实 Butters 我想我们不如早点上床
Well actually, Butters, I think we'd better hit the hay pretty soon.
-但是 这才6点半 -对 我累死了
But, it's only 6:30. - Yeah, and I'm exhausted.
如果你还不困 我有夜间感冒药你可以喝
If you are not sleepy yet, I have some more of that nighttime cold medicine you can drink.
伙计们 我搞到了 是真的
You guys! I got it! It seriously!
这是最伟大的照片！哦老天呐！
It's the greatest picture ever! Oh my God!
-这次Butters做什么了？ -这是天才之作
What'cha do to Butters this time? - It was genius!
我等到他睡熟了 对吧？
I waited till he was totally asleep, right?
然后我拿出照相机 脱下他裤子
And then I got my camera and I pulled down his pants
然后我拍了张他小鸡鸡在我嘴里的照片
and then I took a picture of his wiener in my mouth!
-老兄！ -我知道 我知道 快来看看
Dude! - I know, I know, check it out, look.
他整个小鸡鸡都在我嘴里 看见没？ 哦 哥们 我把他耍得狠吧
I got his whole wiener in my mouth, see? Oh man, I got him good!
老兄 把Butters的鸡鸡放在你嘴里 如何能说是耍了他？
Dude, how is putting Butters wiener in your mouth getting him?
-因为这样就让Butters成了兔子！ -不 老兄 这样让你成了兔子！
Because that makes Butters gay now! - No dude, that makes you gay!
嗯 什么？
Eh... what?
把一个家伙的鸡鸡放在你嘴里 你就成了兔子 傻瓜！
You put a guy's wiener in your mouth, that makes you gay, stupid!
-不会吧 -会的！
Nuh uh. - Yeah huh!
-Kenny 那样不会让我成了兔子 对吧？ -那样他妈的就让你成了兔子
Kenny, that doesn't make me gay, huh? - That makes you very fucking gay.
-但我不是...我不是兔子 伙计们！ -你现在是了
But I'm not- I'm not gay, you guys! - You are now.
-不 不 这是个愚蠢的错误 -无关紧要 你现在是兔子了
No, no, it was a stupid mistake! - Doesn't matter. You're gay now.
不 就几秒钟时间！
No, it was just for a second!
我 我能做什么？我怎样才能变回来？
What, what can I do? How how can I reverse this?
-你不能了 -不 等等
You can't! - No, wait.
-我知道你怎样可以变回来 Cartman. -怎么做？
I know how you can reverse it, Cartman. - How?
唯一抵消的办法就是让Butters 把你的鸡鸡放在嘴里
The only way you can cancel it out is to get Butters to put your wiener in his mouth.
-真的？ -对 这就抵消了你的兔性
Really? - Yeah. Then it cancels out the gay polarity.
狗屎 我得找到Butters
Shit, I gotta find Butters!
白痴
Idiot.
-Butters -嗨 Eric
Butters. - Hey, Eric.
Butters 你猜怎么着 我有个惊喜给你
Butters, guess what? I have a surprise for you.
-惊喜？是什么啊？ -这他妈的很棒的
A surprise? What is it? - It's so fucking awesome.
你会大吃一惊的 这是前所未有的惊喜
You're gonna be soo stoked. It's the best surprise ever!
哦 小子
Oh boy!
-你准备好了？ -好了
You ready? - Yeah!
好了 张开嘴 闭上眼 跪下来
Okay! Just open your mouth and close your eyes and and get on your knees!
哦 好的
Oh, okay!
-等一下下啊 -为什么我看不见了？
Hang on a second here. - How come uh, I can't see?
-因为要不是这样 就不算惊喜了 对吧？ -哦 对的
Cause then it wouldn't be a surprise, would it? - Oh, yeah.
好的 不错 张开嘴巴 Butters
All right, that's good. Okay, open your mouth, Butters?
-做的好 就这样 -嗨！
That's good, just like that. - Hey!
嗨 等一下 这不是耍我的吧？
Hey wait a minute. This ain't a trick, is it?
你不会往我嘴里塞什么恶心东西吧？
Why you're not gonna, stick something icky in my mouth, are ya?
我以我母亲的生命发誓 Butters
I swear on my mother's life, Butters.
我不会往你嘴里塞任何恶心的东西
I am not going to stick anything icky in your mouth.
好的
Okay!
好了 你准备好了？好的 你只要-- 好的 张嘴 好的好的 这就来了
All right, you ready? All right just- Okay, open. Okay, okay, here it comes.
就坐稳了 好吧？我们开始
Just sit very still, okay? Here we go.
-Butters！ -嗨 爸爸！
Butters! - Hey Dad!
-Butters！你在干什么？！ -我在接受惊喜
Butters! What are you doing?! - I'm getting a surprise!
哦 老天！我 我唯一的儿子 堕落成这样子！
Oh my God! My, my only son, reduced to this!
嗨 Eric去哪儿了？
Hey. Where'd Eric go?
Butters 你做这样的事已经多久了？
Butters, how long have you been doing stuff like this?
-什么样的事？ -别对我撒谎 Butters！
Like what? - Don't lie to me, Butters!
我现在知道你的秘密了
I know your secret now!
不 等等 没事 没事 Butters
No wait, wait. It's okay. It's okay, Butters.
这个不是严重的问题 你只不过是有了同性好奇
This isn't a serious problem. You're just bi-curious.
-什么是同性好奇？ -你就是
What's bi-curious? - You are.
只是无害的好奇心 并不能说明什么
Just harmless curiosity and it doesn't mean anything.
我们只需要给你寻求些帮助Butters
We just need to get you some help, Butters.
-你们俩在干什么？ -没事 妈妈 我只不过有点同性好奇
What's going on, you two? - Nothing mom, I'm just a little bi-curious.
Maxi神父 我不知道还有谁可以找
Father Maxi, I just don't know where else to turn.
你看 我才了解到我的儿子有同性好奇
You see, I've just learned that my son is bi-curious.
这是真的吗 孩子？ 你是不是感觉困惑？
Is that true, son? Are you feeling confused?
-对 我非常困惑 -你看见没？
Yeah, I'm pretty confused alright. - You see?
年轻人 你的这些困惑...
Young man, these confused feelings that you're having
只不过是魔鬼试图控制你的方式
are simply the devil's way of trying to get a hold of you.
-真的吗？ -我可以做什么 神父？
Really? - What can I do, Father?
有一个特殊集训营 像你儿子一样感到困惑的年轻人...
There is a special camp where young men who are confused, like your son
可以去利用上帝的力量纯净自己
can go and be cleansed by the power of God.
许多有同性好奇的男孩 在集训营里面被完全治愈了
Many bi-curious boys come out the camp completely cured.
很多有同性好奇的男孩 放在一起的隔离集中营？
A secluded camp where lots of bicurious boys are all put together?
-听上去是个好主意 -哦 伙计 集训营！
That sounds like a good idea. - Whoa boy! Camp!
很好笑！我猜你们以为真的耍到我了！
Very funny! I suppose you really think you got me!
-你说什么呢 肥男？ -我在互联网上查过了 Kyle
What are you talking about, fatass? - I checked on the internet, Kyle.
让Butters含我的小鸡鸡并不会 像你说的一样把我变成兔子！
And getting Butters to put my wiener in his mouth wouldn't make me not gay like you said!
-你搞明白啦？ -没错
You figured that out, huh? - That's right.
从互联网上我还知道 把Butters的小鸡鸡放在我嘴里
And I also learned from the Internet that just because I put Butters wiener in my mouth
并不意味着我就是兔子！
doesn't mean I'm gay!
我所需要做的就是扔掉照片
All I have to do is throw away the picture
忘掉这事 以后没人会知道了
forget it ever happened and nobody will every know.
-除了我们 -对 除了你们
Except for us. - Right, except for you.
和所有我们告诉的人
And all the people we tell.
-你们为什么要告诉别人？ -因为这个真的 真的很搞笑
Why would you tell anybody? - Because it's really, really funny.
不是那么搞笑的 还有很多很多事情要搞笑多了
It's not that funny. There's lots, there's lots of things that are way funnier.
-比如呢？ -比如...
Like what? - Like...
在学校食堂某人的午饭里出现卫生棉棒
a tampon in the school cafeteria, in somebody's lunch.
比如...
Like...
一只狗在一个家伙脸上撇大条
a dog crap, on a guy's face!
-那不好笑 -很好笑
That isn't funny. - Yes, it is!
你们这些家伙 我现在怒了 你们最好别告诉别人
Now you guys, I'm getting pissed off! You'd better not tell anybody!
嗯 我们也许会 也许不会
Well, maybe we will, maybe we won't.
好吧！无所谓！ 你们没有证据说我含Butters的鸡鸡
Fine! Whatever! You guys don't have any proof I put Butters wiener in my mouth!
我们的话将互相矛盾
It will be your word against mine!
我们都知道每个人都更相信我！
And we all know that everyone trusts me way more than you guys!
伙计们 求求你们别告诉别人
You guys, please don't tell anybody.
好的 我们就不告诉别人 只要你从今以后每天对我们超级好
Okay. We won't tell anybody as long as you are supernice to us, every day, from now on.
哦 好吧 你们做梦 好吧 无所谓！
Oh right, like that's possible! Alright, fine!
你知道我会怎么做 Kyle？ 我会回家用Photoshop做那幅照片
You know what I'm gonna do, Kyle?! I'm gonna go home and photoshop the picture
这样就是你含着Butters的鸡鸡
so that it is your face with Butters wiener in his mouth here!
如果你们任何一个告诉任何人 我就会给他们看Kyle的照片
And if any of you say anything to anybody, I'll simply show them the picture of Kyle.
新仁慈集训营 "祈祷不再同性恋"
Camp New Grace "Pray The Gay Away."
大家欢迎我们的新营员 Butters
Everyone, say hello to our new camper, Butters.
嗨 Butters 你好
Hi Butters. Hello. - Hi. Hello Butters.
-非常感谢你们接收他 -别担心
Thank you so much for taking him in. - Don't worry.
你儿子只是需要知道 如果他想正常 他就能正常
Your son just needs to learn that he can be straight if he chooses to be.
-你知道你为什么来集训营吗 Butters？ -因为我有点同性好奇？
Do you know why you're here at camp, Butters? - Because I'm bi-curious?
没错 跟所有营员一样 你很困惑 你不知道出路何在
That's right. Like all the campers here, you're confused and you don't think there's a way out.
但是尽管有人已经让你相信 你不能控制自己所想
But even though some people would have you believe you can't control how you feel
实情是耶稣基督的力量可以让你正常
the truth is that with the power of Jesus Christ you can be normal.
现在 为了确保你在营里不再犯错
Now, just to make sure you don't slip up while in camp
我们给每个营员安排了一位责任人
we assign every camper an accountabilibuddy.
我们见一见Ryan 你的责任人
Let's meet Ryan, your accountabilibuddy.
Ryan以为他永远不能改变了
Ryan thought he could never change.
但是现在他知道了 借助耶稣的力量和祈祷
But now he's learning that with the power of Christ and prayer
他能拥有全新的人生
he can have a whole new life.
这边有食堂 三餐都在这里
Over this way we have the cafeteria. All the meals are served there.
Bradley 你做Butters的责任人如何？
Bradley! How about you be Butters' accountabilibuddy?
所以你们要自卑 服在神大能的手下 到时他必叫你们升高 彼得前书 5:6
Humble yourselves therefore under God's mighty hand, that he may lift you up. Peter 5:6
Butters是营里的新人 他被选中来接触自己的痛苦
Butters here is new to the camp. He's chosen to rid himself of his affliction
与耶稣基督结成亲密关系
and forge a personal relationship with Jesus Christ.
我有同性好奇
I'm bi-curious.
不可像与女人一样与男人苟合 这本是可憎恶的 利未记 18:22.
Do not lie with a man as one lies with a woman, that is detestible. Leviticus 18:22.
这就对了 Bradley 我想你正在被治好
That's right, Bradley. I think we're well on our way to being healed.
-又有一个 22号房 -哦 该死的
We've got another one, room 22. - Oh, darnit!
-哦 哥们 我得配个高分辨率光谱仪 -好了 轮到我了
Aw man, I've got H O R S now. - Okay, my turn.
东西在哪儿 你这个猥琐犹太人？
Where is it, you filthy jew?
-什么在哪儿？ -你他妈的肯定知道的
Where's what? - You know goddamn well what!
-放开我 -你到底在干吗 Cartman？
Let go of me. - What the hell are you doing, Cartman?!
我回家去想把那张我含Butters 阳物的照片改成Kyle
I went home to alter the picture of me with Butters penis in my mouth to look like Kyle
但是找不到了！
but it was gone!
-你把我照片拿哪儿去了？ -放手！我没拿你的傻照片！
What did you do with my picture?! - Knock it off! I don't have your stupid picture!
-还给我 Kyle -我没拿
Give it back, Kyle! - I don't have it!
我向上帝发誓 Kyle 如果你现在不还给我
I swear to God, Kyle, if you don't give it back right now
我会在这儿打断你操蛋的犹太腿!
I'm gonna break your fucking Jew legs right here!
-闭嘴！ -你闭嘴！
Shut up! - You shut up!
你在撒谎 你们俩在给他打掩护
You're lying and you two are covering up for him!
知道吗 你们就跟犹太人一样了
You know what? You're just like Jews yourselves!
Stan 你是犹太人 Kenny 你是犹太人 你们都是犹太人
Stan, you're a Jew and Kenny, you're a Jew! You're all Jews!
主因此爱之
The Lord is love this for
有了基督 我不再困惑
With Jesus I can just say no and not be confused anymore.
我们现在聆听菲利普牧师的布道
We will now hear a sermon from Pastor Phillips.
新来的营员们
For those of you who are new to camp
菲利普牧师曾慧剑斩情丝 不再有与你们一样的痛苦
Pastor Phillips is somebody who has broken free of the bonds that afflict you.
他也有同性好奇？
He's bi-curious too?
不再有了 因为菲利普牧师祈祷了
Not anymore. Because Pastor Phillips prayed
经耶稣基督之手 他已经痊愈了
and by the hand of Jesus Christ he's now completely cured!
让我们听听菲利普牧师的故事 孩子们
Let's hear it for Pastor Phillips, kids!
你们好 营员们
Hello, campers!
是的无论你是否相信 我自己曾有不洁的欲望
Yes, believe it or not, I myself used to have unclean urges
跟你们很多人一样 我以为我天生如此 没有选择
and like a lot of you I thought I was just made that way, that I didn't have a choice.
但我意识到上帝不想我们如此
But then I realized that God didn't want me to be that way!
上帝想让我们成为男人！
God wanted me to be a man!
所以我穿上我的西装 祈祷能变正常 你们猜如何？
So I buckled up in my little suit and I prayed to be normal and guess what?
这样做很有用！
It worked!
没错 孩子们 你看 现在你们就像回形针
That's right, kids. You see, right now you're like a paper clip.
就像回形针一样 上帝需要扳动你 塑造你
And just like a paper clip, God needs to bend you and shape you
让你变直 （双关语：直等于正常）
and make you straight.
公园县警察局
Park County Police Station
-你说你被抢劫了？ -是的 一张照片
So you say you were robbed. - Yes. A photograph.
我知道谁抢的 他的名字是Kyle Broflovski
And I know who took it! His name is Kyle Broflovski!
如果是张照片 有什么大不了的？ 你再打印一张不就行了
If it's a photo, what's the big deal? Why don't you just print out another one?
事情很大条啊 那张照片是我的财产 我要它回来
It's a big deal, okay?! That picture is my property and I want it back!
好吧 这张是什么照片？
Okay, what is the picture of?
那个有什么关系？
Why does that matter?
不知道是什么照片 我们怎么去找它？
Well how are we gonna find your picture unless we know what it is?
-好吧 是关于我的照片 -还有呢？
All right. It's a picture of me. - Yes?
这张照片上有我...
It's a picture of me...
和一个看上去象阳物的东西...
and what appears to be a penis...
在我嘴里
in my mouth.
-你在吃别人的阳物？ -不 不 我没有
You were sucking somebody's penis. - No, no, I was not!
我睡着了 这个人把阳物放在我嘴里 我当时不知道
I was asleep and this person just puts a penis in my mouth without me knowing!
然后他拍了照片
And and took the picture!
-我明白了 -是的
I see. - Yes.
可能看上去在照片里 阳物就在我嘴里的时候
Now it may appear in the picture that I'm actually looking at the camera lens and smiling
我在笑着看照相机镜头 还竖起拇指
with the penis in my mouth and giving a thumbs up.
但我向你保证 我在熟睡中
But I assure you, I was fast asleep!
好吧 我们得先申请 由初审陪审团批准的搜捕令
Well we'd have to get a warrant first, approved by a grand jury
我没时间了 明天就要上学了
I don't have time for that! We have school tomorrow!
我知道Kyle会在宣讲课上 给每个人看那张照片
And I know that Kyle is gonna show the picture to everybody during Show and Tell!
那样的话 你就惨了
Well then, you're screwed.
你们两个都明白我们在努力拯救 你们的灵魂于永恒的地狱生活 对吧？
You both do understand that we're trying to save your souls from eternal life in hell?
当然 我想
Well sure, I guess.
只有通过基督我们才能洗净自己的灵魂
Only through Christ can we cleanse our souls.
你们也知道有条规矩声明 不允许看不纯洁或不道德的图片？
And you do know the rule which states that no impure or immoral images are allowed to be seen by the eye?
是的 当然
Well yeah, sure.
让我们洁净自己 除去身体灵魂一切的污秽
So let's purify ourselves from everything that makes the body or soul unclean.
哥林多后书 第七章
Corinthians, chapter 7.
那你们介不介意告诉我们 为什么我们可以在你们房间找到1979年希尔斯男士内衣目录？
Then do you mind telling us why we found this, 1979 Sears mens underwear catalog in your room?
是我的
That's mine.
你知道这是严格禁止的！
You know this is strictly forbidden!
我不明白 内衣有什么问题
Ah I don't understand. What's wrong with underwear?
什么问题？！ 这就是让你困惑的东西
What's wrong?! This is what makes you confused!
你不明白吗？ 这个就在让你困惑 不是吗？
Don't you get it?! This is confusing you right now, isn't it?!
是的 这些都很令人困惑
Yes, it's all very confusing!
这也是你的错 Butters Bradley是你的责任人
This is just as much your fault, Butters! Bradley is your accountabilibuddy!
你得负上连带责任
That makes you accountabilibuddyable.
你们俩的行为威胁到 我们所有拯救这里孩子的努力
Both of your boys behavior has jeopardizing all of the work we're doing here to save these kids!
对 因为在房间里有违禁品 你们两个将在接下来四天手抄圣经
Right. For having contraband in your room, you will both do penance
以作忏悔
by writing scripture for the next four days!
那个婊子养的 他会给每个人看照片
That son of a bitch. He's gonna show everyone that picture.
只有十二个小时了
Only twelve hours from now.
就这样 我没有选择了 我不得不把妈妈拉进来
That's it. I don't have a choice. I'm gonna have to bring mom in on this one!
我不得不告诉她真相
I'm going to have to tell her the truth.
Eric？出什么 出什么事了？
Eric? What's the, what's the matter?
我明天不想去学校
I don't wanna go to school tomorrow.
甜心 告诉妈妈怎么了
Sweetie, tell mommy what happened.
Kyle有我一张照片 他会在宣讲课上给每个人看
Kyle, has a picture of me and he's gonna show everyone during Show and Tell.
大家都会笑话我
And everyone's gonna laugh at me.
哦 那为什么他会这么做？
Oh, now why would he do that?
因为他嫉妒我比他聪明
Because, he's jealous of how much smarter I am than him.
所以他会给每个人看那张照片
So, he's gonna show everyone the picture.
什么样的照片 Eric？
What is the picture of, Eric?
上次Butters来过夜的时候 我对他真的很好
Last time, when Butters spent the night, I was being really nice to him
我想给他拍张照片给他妈妈看
and I was gonna take a picture of him for his mom to have.
哦 那很好啊
Oh, that's nice.
但是 就在我拍完照片以后 Butters变得很热
But then, right when I took the picture, Butters got really hot
他就脱了脱了他的裤扣子 然后我跌倒了
so he pulled his pajama bottoms down and then I tripped and fell down
我的嘴巴正好对上他的阳物 当时我想到一些搞笑的事情
and my mouth landed right on his penis and then I thought of something funny
所以我就笑了 照相机就拍到了 还有竖着拇指
so I smiled up at, the camera and gave like a, thumbs up
Kyle拿走了照片 他要给每个人看了
and then Kyle took the picture from me and he's gonna show it to everybody
让他们以为我是兔子
and make them think I'm gay.
哦 过来 甜心 没事的
Oh, there there, sweetie. It'll be okay.
这些事情常有的
These things happen.
但是妈妈 我试过拿回照片 他就是不肯给
But, mom, I've been trying to get the picture back, but he won't give it to me.
没事 Eric 我来跟Kyle的妈妈谈谈
It's okay, Eric. I'll have a talk with Kyle's mother.
你会谈？
You will?
但他爱我们 派他唯一的儿子 来赎我们的罪孽
But that he loved us and sent his only son to be the satisfaction of our sins.
五十份！
Neato!
-Butters我很抱歉把你扯进来 -哦 没事 Bradley
Butters, I'm sorry for getting you into trouble. - Aw, that's okay, Bradley.
我真的想变好
I really want to get better.
我努力做每一件辅导员说的事 但不知怎的 我始终感觉困惑
I try to do everything the counselors say, but somehow I still feel confused.
嗯 希望我们写完这些经文
Yeah, well hopefully, when we finish writing all these verses
我们不再有同性好奇 就可以回家了
we won't be bi-curious no more and then we can go home!
你真的很棒 Butters 我是说 我觉得你很好
You're really terrific, Butters. I mean, I think you're great.
哦 上帝！坏思想！坏思想！
Oh God! Bad thought! Bad thought!
-怎么了？ -我想 我想我喜欢你
What's the matter? - I think, I think I like you.
-我也喜欢你 Bradley -真的吗？
Well I like you too, Bradley. - You do?
-是的 -你喜欢喜欢我？
Well, yeah! - You like like me?
当然 我喜欢喜欢你多多的
Sure, I like like you a lot a lot.
哦上帝 我们都是不可救药的 你没看出来我们注定失败吗？
Oh God, we're both unfixable! Don't you see we're lost causes?!
我们是邪恶的 没有什么可以改变我们
We're just evil and nothing can change us!
没有出路了 Butters 我们不得不自杀
There's no other way out, Butters! We have to kill ourselves!
不 Bradley 你不能离开 你是我的责任人
No! Bradley! You can't leave, you're my accountabilibuddy!
-你好 -你好 Sheila。我是Liane，Eric的妈妈
Hello? - Hello, Sheila? It's Liane, Eric's mother.
哦 你好 Cartman夫人
Oh, hello, Mrs. Cartman.
Sheila 我很抱歉麻烦你
Sheila, I'm sorry to trouble you with this
不过很明显你的儿子有一张 Eric含着其他男孩阳物的照片
but apparently your son has a picture of Eric with another boy's penis in his mouth.
对不起？
Excuse me?
别担心 甜心 没问题了
Don't worry, sweetie, everything is fine.
没问题了？真的？
It is? Really?
哦 妈妈 谢谢你 谢谢你
Oh, mommy, thank you! Thank you!
你明天在学校不用担心了
You have nothing to worry about in school tomorrow.
Broflovski夫人向我保证 Kyle没有拿那张照片
Mrs. Broflovski assured me that Kyle doesn't have the picture.
什么？
What?
她和她儿子谈过了 说他没有拿
She talked with her son and says he doesn't have it.
-妈妈 她在撒谎 -她说她保证 Eric
Mom, she's lying! - She said she was sure, Eric.
妈妈 你根本不了解犹太人 他们一直在撒谎
Mom, you don't know anything about Jews! They lie all the time!
Eric 我做不了更多的了
Well, Eric, there's nothing more I can do about it.
只能如此了 Kyle赢了
Then that's it. Kyle wins.
但是他不会完全胜利
But he won't win completely!
我会打印另一份照片 自己给全班看
I'm going to print out another copy of that picture and show it to the class myself!
我至少能够抢掉他最终的大笑
I can at least rob Kyle of his final laugh.
你介不介意告诉我们 你是怎样丢掉你的责任人的？
Do you mind telling me how you managed to lose your accountabilibuddy?!
我去找他的 但他跑的太快了
I went looking for him, but he runs real fast.
你看起来没把这个集训营当回事 Butters
You don't seem to take this camp seriously, Butters.
-我已经打电话叫你爸爸来谈谈了 -哦 不 我爸爸？
I've called your father in for a talk. - Oh no, my dad?
你明不明白地狱的概念？
Do you understand the concept of hell?
你有没有意识到如果我们不治好你 你就会在火海中燃烧直至永远？
Do you realize that if we don't fix you, you will burn in a lake of fire for eternity?
嗯 是的 但是我不是很明白 你们在治疗什么
Well yeah, but I just don't quite understand what you're fixing.
-我们在治疗你的困惑 -你在这儿 Butters
We're fixing your confusion! - There you are, Butters!
-哦 嗨 爸爸 -他做了什么？
Oh, hey dad. - What's he done now?!
Stotch先生 你的儿子很顽固 他不愿意改变 更糟的是
Mr. Stotch, your son is insubordinate, unwilling to change and worse yet
他丢了他的责任人
he's lost his accountabilibuddy!
他们找到他了！他们找到Bradley了！ 你们最好快点
They found him! They found Bradley! You'd better come quick!
哦天上的主啊！不要跳 Bradley！
Oh Lord in Heaven! Don't jump, Bradley!
退 退后！上帝憎恶我！
Stay back! I'm an abomination of God!
不 我们在治疗你！
No, we're fixing you!
我猜你以为今天是大日子 啊 Kyle? 想在大伙面前羞辱我？
Guess you think today is your big day, huh Kyle? To embarrass me in front of everyone?
你猜怎么着？我不会让你得逞的！
Well guess what? I'm not giving you the satisfaction!
好的 学生们 我们上课
Okay students, let's all take our seats.
今天是礼拜一 我们照往常一样从宣讲开始
Since it is Monday, we'll start as always with Show And Tell.
谁想第一个来？
Who'd like to go first?
哦！放弃吧 老兄！
Ow! Quit it, dude!
好的 Eric 老天 冷静下来 你可以第一个来
Okay Eric, Jesus, calm down. You can go first.
在今天的宣讲会上 我想和你们分享一些非常特别的
For Show And Tell today, I would like to share with you some very special,
在追求成为受尊敬的摄影家的道路上 我拍摄的非常艺术的照片
very artsy photographs I've taken in pursuit of being a respected photographer.
第一张照片我称其为“冬天的心情”
This first picture I like to call "Moods of Winter."
一幅简单的高黑白对比度的 白杨林照片
A simple aspen grove shot in high-contrast black and white
表现了树干的痛苦 使我们想起死亡
shows the brittleness of the trunks and reminds one of death.
这幅照片是我在日出时拍摄 这个孤独的人正步行上班
This picture I took just as the sun was rising and this lonely man was walking to work.
也许表达了我们所有的孤独？
A statement about all of our loneliness, perhaps?
他不会想给每个人看--
He isn't actually going to show everyone.
下一张照片...
And now this next picture...
别跳 Bradley 你只会让上帝对你更加生气
Don't jump, Bradley! You will only make god angrier with you!
太晚了
It's too late.
Bradley 求你了 你是我的责任人 你这样让我怎么见人？
Bradley, please. You're my accountabilibuddy. How will this make me look?
你退后 你只会让事情更糟
You get back. You're only gonna make things worse.
我不正常 我永远不会正常了
I'm not normal. I'll never be normal!
-你完全正常 Bradley -退后 你跟他一样困惑
You're perfectly normal, Bradley. - Get back! You're just as confused as he is!
好吧 好吧 就这样了
All right. All right that does it!
我恶心和厌倦了每个人 告诉我说我很困惑
I am sick and tired of everyone telling me I'm confused!
在其他人说我困惑之前 我根本不困惑
I wasn't confused until other people started telling me I was!
你知道我怎么想的吗？ 我想有可能是你们困惑了！
You know what I think? I think maybe you are the ones who are confused!
是啊
Yeah.
我不再仅仅因为你们说我困惑 我就困惑下去了
I'm not gonna be confused anymore just because you say I should be!
我的名字叫Butters 我八岁 我的血型是O型 我有同性好奇
My name is Butters, I'm eight years old, I'm blood type O and I'm bi-curious!
即便如此也不要紧 因为如果我有同性好奇 我也是上帝因某种原因造出来的
And even that's okay! Because if I'm bi-curious and I'm somehow made from God.
我想上帝自己一定也有点同性好奇
Then I think your God must be a little bi-curious himself!
我认为 我认为我现在想下来了
I think. I think I'd like to come down now.
他要下来了 我们做到了
He's coming down! We did it!
借助基督的力量 我们拯救了这个孩子
Through the power of Christ we have saved this child!
Butters 我想我们也可以回家了
Well Butters, I guess we might as well go home.
-看上去你永远不会改变了 -不了 我喜欢有点同性好奇
Looks like you're never gonna change. - No. I like being bi-curious.
你知道吗？我也是
Well you know something? So do I.
等等 我现在困惑了
Wait. Now I am confused.
这张照片是我在电厂附近拍摄的日落
And this photograph I took of a sunset near the power plant.
注意着对比强烈的画面表达了 我们对于地球深深的影响
Note how the contrasting images make a statement about our impact on the Earth.
接着是我最后一张照片
Which brings us to my last picture.
这张照片你们可能觉得有点争议性
This picture you may find somewhat controversial.
老兄
Dude.
是的 这张照片以5.6光圈 使用低光滤镜拍摄
Yes. This is shot at a 5.6 aperture using a low-light filter.
你可以看见高速胶片上的颗粒
You can see the grain from the high-speed film...
这里大概有个阳物在我嘴里
there's sort of a penis in my mouth right here...
场地的低深度使得背景柔和
and the low depth of field keeps the background soft.
Eric 这到底是什么？
Eric, what the hell is this?!
这里是一个反对伊拉克战争的声明
What this is, is a statement against the war in Iraq.
我们的军队还在伊拉克是错误的 是错误的！
It's wrong that we still have our troops there. It's wrong!
-我认为-- -Eric Cartman？
And what I think that- - Eric Cartman?
我们收到你妈妈的紧急信息
We got an emergency message from your mother?
别放照片 Kyle没拿
Do not show picture. Kyle didn't have it after all.
在你桌底找到了
Found it under your desk.
她说你知道是什么意思 好吧？
She said you'd know what that means, mkay?
靠
Lame.
翻译：sansanfeng @ 1000fr.com 校对：sansanfeng @ 1000fr.com
Transcript: spscriptorium Sync: muter - forom.com
双语合成 Lv&daisy